leerburg.com 2015-06-11

# Leerburg | Information about our Organization and Website

� **Information about our Organization and Website**

Information about our Organization and Website

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. We are based in the USA.

Our principal activity is: Produce and sell dog training videos and equipment and provide dog training information. Our privacy policy covers Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. and its web site.

Organization name: | Leerburg Enterprises, Inc.   
---|---  
Address: | PO Box 218  
City, State, Zip: | Menomonie, WI 54751  
Country: | USA  
Controller: | Ed Frawley  
Web Site: | http://leerburg.com  
Phone | 715.235.6502  
  
**Newsletter Policy**

Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. sends out a newsletter. The following people will receive this newsletter unless they opt-out and chose not to receive it:

> 1 - Customers who purchase products from Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. 
> 
> 2 - People who write and ask that one of our catalogs be sent through the United States Postal Service
> 
> 3 - People how specifically ask to be placed out our newsletter mailing list.
> 
> 4 - People who send Leerburg Enterprises, Inc. emails with questions on dog training.
> 
> 5 - Anyone who registers for the Leerburg Dog Training web forum.

Every newsletter has an opt-out option at the top and the bottom of the newsletter. If a person does not wish to receive our newsletter, they simply click the opt-out link and they will automatically be added to the list of people who no longer receive our newsletter. 

We do not sell our email lists nor do we sell our mailing lists.

I want to make it very clear that Leerburg will never sell customer information to other online data collection companies. Not ever! We have been asked many times to rent our mailing list. We will never do that, much less pass on customer information to a third party. 

I take the stewardship of our customer's personal information very seriously. I don’t want my personal information shared with someone who is influenced by the highest bidder, and I assume our customers feel the same way.

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

You can access our website home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.

**The services and links of our Web sites**

Our web site do not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.

Our websites do not include links to third party web service providers.

**Automatic Collection of Information**

We only use cookies for our shopping cart system & webboard. They are used for the functionality of the web site and are not used to track any personal information.

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals.

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.

If we wish to use your personal data for new purposes, we offer you the means to consent to those new purposes:

> By sending an email - jeff@leerburg.com  
>  By sending postal mail to this address - PO Box 218, Menomonie, WI 54751  
>  By calling this telephone number - 715.235.6502

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by:

Additionally, to ensure that children's privacy is respected on our web site, we:

  * Do not enter information given to us by people under the age of 18 into our mailing list database.

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data.

Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations.

**Confidentiality**

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data:

  * Primary personal data (such as name and contact details)   

  * Identifiers (such as credit card details, web site password)

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:

  * Unauthorized access   

  * Improper use or disclosure   

  * Unauthorized modification   

  * Unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.  

**Security**

We here at Leerburg Enterprises make safety of your private information a #1 priority. Where possible we put the highest safe guards on data and adhere to all industry standards on data security. 

Orders are placed through a high grade 128-bit encrypted HTTPS connection. Orders are received by Leerburg over a secure, private, encrypted connection. Some information (like your email order receipt) is transferred over email, but does not contain vital information like credit card numbers, expiration dates or CVV2 Codes. Orders are processed & fulfilled by (background-checked) employees at a secure facility in Menomonie, Wisconsin. Order Records are stored digitally on a secure server with limited access (CVV2 information is not kept past processing). Paper records are securely stored for the legal number of years required per credit card company policy. Paper records do not have credit card details printed on them. We do not store any card information past the point of processing. We are fully PCI compliant.  

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you**

You can ask us, by:

  * Sending an email - jeff@leerburg.com  

  * Sending postal mail to this address - PO Box 218, Menomonie, WI 54751  

  * Calling this telephone number - 715.235.6502

Upon request, which you can indicate by:

  * Sending an email - jeff@leerburg.com  

  * Sending postal mail to this address - PO Box 218, Menomonie, WI 54751  

  * Calling this telephone number - 715.235.6502

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week, although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge.

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

  * Erased   

  * Rectified or amended   

  * Completed

We do not reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.  

**Privacy Compliance**

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization.

In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are:

  * Voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure

**Self Assessment Procedure:**

Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service:  | Ed Frawley  
---|---  
URL: | http://leerburg.com  
Address: | PO Box 218  
Menomonie, WI 54751  
Country | USA  
  
**Privacy Support:**

If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:

  | Contact 1   
---|---  
Name/Designation: | Ed Frawley  
Dept/Title: | Owner  
Address: | PO Box 218  
Menomonie, WI 54751  
Phone Number: | 715.235.6502  
Fax Number: | 715.235.8868  
Email Address: | jeff@leerburg.com  
URL: | http://leerburg.com  
  
We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed.

**TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used**

x Volunteered by each visitor  
\- Collected from public records or bodies  
\- Collected from private organizations

Primary Personal Data | Technical Administration of the Web Site | Research & Development | Customer Administration |   
Marketing |   
Trading in Personal Data  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Name: | 

-

| 

-

| 

X

| 

X

| 

-  
  
Gender: | 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-  
  
Address: | 

-

| 

-

| 

X

| 

X

| 

-  
  
Email Address: | 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

X

| 

-  
  
Phone/Fax: | 

-

| 

-

| 

X

| 

-

| 

-  
  
Other: | 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-

| 

-  
  
**Other personal details and profiling data is not collected**

These include data that is:

\- Volunteered by each visitor

  * Personal Details   

  * Physical Description   

  * Family Characteristics   

  * Education   

  * Lifestyle   

  * Financial Resources   

  * Other

\- Collected from public records or bodies  
\- Collected from private organizations
